# ABHISHEK RAMESH KUMAR

### DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER

### Contact

+91 95609 88375

abhishekrk41@gmail.com

YouTube

Blog

in LinkedIn

Bengaluru, India

### Skills

- Technical Expertise: Python, MS Office- Word and Excel, Brandwatch, Konnect Insights, Freshdesk, Partoo, OneDirect, Locobuzz, Salesrobot, Apollo.io, Seamless.ai, Mautic, Hostinger
- LinkedIn Certification: "Decision-Making in High Stress Situations", "Jodi Glickman on Pitching Yourself"
- Udemy Certification: Adobe Premiere Pro CC Masterclass: Video Editing in Premiere, Excel Essentials: The Complete Excel Series - Level 1, 2 & 3, 100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 2023

### Languages

- English
  Tamil
- French Hindi

# Volunteering

May (2021) Hemkunt Foundation

Feb (2019) **Teach India** 

### Education

2015 Ram-Eesh International

School, Greater Noida

PCM, 88%

2021 Indian Institute of

Technology- Madras,

Chennai

Ongoing BS Data Analytics and Programming, 7.9 CGPA

### Introduction

I am Abhishek and here's a little bit about myself. I love reading books and one of them was The Psychology of Money by Morgan Housel. My favorite part of the book was the last chapter not because it meant that I was closer to finishing it and finally could put it down, but actually because the author says something that resonated with me.

He said there "can often be a mile-wide gap between what makes sense—which is what people suggest you do—and what feels right to them—which is what they actually do". The fundamental fact that there is no one universal truth bracketing all is wisdom.

I like playing Chess in my free time and own a blog titled Solitude (bigfootguyblog.wordpress.com). I am part of the Delhi Beatboxing Community. As for work experience, I have experience in digital media marketing, ORM, and running campaigns.

## Work Experience

Argusoft

Jul 2024 - Nov 2024

Business Development Manager, Full time, Gandhinagar, India (Ran campaigns; used Apollo and Hubspot to reach out for pitch calls

and meetings).

Ai-Ris LLC

Feb 2024 - Jul 2024

Sales Development Manager, Full time, Austin, Texas (Outreach done on LinkedIn and mails to

prospective investor partners)

Navyug Infosolutions

Apr 2023 - Jan 2024

Digital Marketing Manager, Full time, Noida, India (Ran campaigns on LinkedIn and mails; worked hand in hand with the sales department in understanding the needs of

clients' software solutions needs)

RepIndia

Dec 2020 - Apr 2023

ORM Senior Executive, Full time, Delhi, India (Managed social media platforms for brands like Adani Group, Adani Airports, Enrich Salons, Suzuki India, Tata Trusts, made presentations on their listening to better CRM, made pitches,

made detailed analytical reports)

AdFactors PRMay 2022 – Aug 2022

Consultant, Part Time,

Delhi, India (Made pitches and analytical ORM reports)

# Positions Of Responsibility

- Member, Inferno- Dance club of Shiv Nadar University, 2015-2018
- Member, Hustle- Dance crew, 2015-2016
- Organizer- SNUBIK's: SNU Open, 2017
- Organizer- Equal Conference, 2017
- Organizer, Campus Caravan- Slam Poetry event, 2017
- Attendee- TEDx Shiv Nadar University, 2018
- Member, Delhi Beatbox Community, 2021- present
   Member- Mukhavaran Theatre Group, 2021
- RepIndia Rockstar (Employee of the Quarter), Q3 2022-2023